"Only for love"
"오직 사랑을 위해서"
Section (10)
섹션 (10)
(delete list)
(목록 삭제)
(good Morning)
(좋은 아침이에요)
Oh yeah, now we can use the witch
아, 이제 마녀를 사용할 수 있겠네요
(I have an appointment today, but I can't see it anymore)
(오늘 약속이 있는데 더 이상 볼 수 없어요)
(I also have an appointment today)
(저도 오늘 약속이 있어요)
(I can't see you anymore)
(더 이상 당신을 볼 수 없습니다)
(Good morning.. I am sending a heart picture)
(좋은 아침.. 하트 사진을 보내드립니다)
(don't forget the concert tonight)
(오늘 밤 콘서트를 잊지 마세요)
(Do you want to have dinner together?)
(저녁 같이 드실래요?)
Well, let it go.. It's good not to do extra
뭐 놔두세요.. 추가로 안하는게 좋아요
I don't want to give up
포기하고 싶지 않아
Line up and enter in order
줄을 서서 순서대로 입장하세요
Coincidentally
우연히도
Coincidence?
우연의 일치?
I was invited, right?
나는 초대받았죠?
Did I invite you?
내가 당신을 초대했나요?
The one I invited
내가 초대한 사람
(a moment)
(순간)
(Xiang)
(샹)
(SW)
(SW)
(Shiyu?)
(시유?)
I'm just kidding
장난이야
You came because I didn't want to talk to you again
너랑 다시 얘기하고 싶지 않아서 왔어
It really coincides
정말 일치하네요
That's what I said
그게 내가 말한거야
Will they come in?
그들이 들어올까요?
Well, of course
물론이죠
Why?
왜?
This song is really sad
이 노래 진짜 슬프다
I am very sad
나는 매우 슬프다
I'm so sad
난 너무 슬퍼
Sister Shuyi recently broke up with her boyfriend?
슈이 언니는 최근 남자친구와 헤어졌다고요?
Is that why you are so emotional?
그래서 그렇게 감정적인가요?
We broke up last month
우리 지난달에 헤어졌어
He completely cheated on me
그 사람은 나를 완전히 속였어
But that doesn't make it easy to get emotional
하지만 그렇다고 해서 감정이 쉽게 생기지는 않습니다.
I keep thinking about it
계속 생각나는데
When you break up
헤어질 때
It shouldn't be only women who feel sad
슬픈 감정을 느끼는 것은 여자만이 아니다.
Only bad guys should die
나쁜 놈들만 죽어야 해
My sister is absolutely right
언니 말이 완전 옳아
But in the form of sister Shuyi
하지만 슈이 자매의 모습으로
I can't believe that my sister was cheated on
내 여동생이 바람을 피웠다는 걸 믿을 수 없어
My sister is very beautiful
내 여동생은 정말 아름다워요
Yes, right?
네, 그러죠?
But it happened
하지만 그런 일이 일어났어요
Because that guy is blind
그 사람은 눈이 멀었 으니까
He dreams of money more than looks
외모보다 ​​돈을 꿈꾸는 남자
The rich girl he is chasing has an uncle who has a lot of money
그가 쫓고 있는 부자 소녀 에게는 돈이 많은 삼촌이 있다
Sister Shuyi
슈이 자매
My sister handled it delicately
언니가 섬세하게 처리해줬어
I really respect my sister
나는 내 여동생을 정말 존경한다.
But he got along well with his uncle
하지만 그는 삼촌과 잘 지냈어요
I realized that he is a really good person
그 사람 정말 좋은 사람이라는 걸 깨달았어요
So now I can't share
그래서 지금은 공유할 수 없어요
So what are you waiting for?
그래서 당신은 무엇을 기다리고 있습니까?
I will say don't overthink it
너무 깊게 생각하지 말라고 말할게
I have lost my sister's ex-boyfriend
나는 내 여동생의 전 남자친구를 잃었다
Don't lose this new guy
이 새로운 사람을 잃지 마세요
But isn't he as bad as his cousin?
하지만 그 사람은 그의 사촌만큼 나쁘지 않나요?
No, she was completely different from her niece
아니요, 그녀는 조카와 전혀 달랐습니다
My sister Shuyi is going home
내 여동생 슈이가 집에 가는데
- Be sure to drive - bye bye
- 꼭 운전하세요 - 안녕
(Professor Yu)
(유 교수)
(Is he a fan of Mom?)
(그 사람은 엄마 팬인가요?)
Mom.. When Mom debuted
엄마.. 엄마가 데뷔했을 때
Give me some limited edition albums?
한정판 앨범 좀 주실래요?
You can't find it in any of the music releases
어떤 음반에서도 찾을 수 없습니다
Rage
격노
Coincidentally
우연히도
I met you here at the shop of Professor Yu
여기 유교수님 가게에서 만났어요
I gave you a ticket to Xi'an, so I came to relax
시안행 티켓을 주셨으니 쉬러 왔어요
You've already seen the interview draft
이미 인터뷰 초안을 보셨을 겁니다
Can I schedule an interview this week ?
이번 주에 인터뷰 일정을 잡을 수 있나요?
No problem.. What if it's 3pm on Tuesday next week ?
문제없습니다.. 다음주 화요일 오후 3시라면 어떨까요?
Good son
좋은 아들
I will drive you home
집까지 데려다줄게
I will hire a taxi
택시를 빌릴게요
Well then, take care
그럼 조심하세요
Turkish
터키어
(When you come to me)
(네가 나에게 올 때)
(You have to take this chance and pretend to be an accident)
(이 기회를 잡아서 사고인 척 해야지)
Director Xi, I broke my ankle
시 감독님, 발목이 부러졌어요
All because of you
모든게 너 때문이야
You should be responsible
당신은 책임을 져야합니다
Why should I be responsible?
왜 내가 책임을 져야 합니까?
Because every time I see you, I can't focus on the road
널 볼 때마다 길에 집중이 안 되니까
(Where is my sister?)
(내 여동생은 어디에 있나요?)
I will come to you from there
나는 거기에서 당신에게 올 것이다
Did Shi Xian really do it? Shi Xian
Shi Xian이 정말 그랬나요? Shi Xian
God.. why am I so unlucky?
맙소사.. 나는 왜 이렇게 운이 좋지 않은 걸까요?
Shi Xiang is a heartless person
Shi Xiang은 무정한 사람입니다.
cruel
잔혹한
Am I not beautiful?
나는 아름답지 않은가?
Am I pathetic?
내가 한심한 걸까?
Your eyes are not just farsighted
당신의 눈은 단지 원시적인 것이 아닙니다
Avoid handsome people
잘생긴 사람은 피하세요
People like you have to grow old alone.. no..
너같은 사람은 혼자 늙어가야지.. 안돼..
Continue.. What's left?
계속하세요.. 무엇이 남았나요?
What should a people like me do without?
나 같은 사람은 없이 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Director Xi
시 감독
I think I can explain to you in the car, what do you think?
차 안에서 설명드릴 수 있을 것 같은데, 어떻게 생각하시나요?
You still haven't come up with a solution?
아직도 해결책을 찾지 못하셨나요?
What's the rush?
서두르는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Even the exam is given 90 minutes to answer
시험도 답하는데 90분이 주어지는데
So sick..
너무 아파..
It definitely hits the bone
확실히 뼈에 닿는다
It hurts so much
그것은 너무 많이 아파요
Still a lot to talk about
아직 얘기할 게 많다.
(outpatient)
(외래환자)
Go out.. Take me to the doctor and have a bone scan
나가서.. 의사한테 데려가서 뼈스캔 좀 받아봐
My leg hurts
다리가 아파요
I can't stand up, I'm sure I can't walk
일어서지 못하겠어 분명 걷지도 못하겠지
If it wasn't for you, I wouldn't have dislocated my ankle
네가 아니었으면 발목이 탈구되지도 않았을 텐데
You should take responsibility for this
이에 대한 책임을 져야 한다
Keng Shuyi.. I'm exaggerating
켕슈이.. 과장이네
I am not exaggerating
나는 과장하지 않는다
Can't you be a little more lenient?
좀 더 관대해질 수는 없나요?
Is your heart made of stone, director Xi?
시 감독님 , 당신의 마음은 돌로 만들어졌나요 ?
No
아니요
- So.. - You said yourself.. that I don't have a heart
- 그럼.. - 나한테 심장이 없다고 스스로 말했잖아..
Why are you so petty?
왜 이렇게 사소해?
Try wearing these shoes and see if they dislocate
이 신발을 신어보고 탈구되는지 확인해보세요
It hurts like a broken ankle
발목 부러진 것처럼 아프다
You know, it hurts so much that I can't stand it
있잖아 너무 아파서 견딜 수가 없어
You've never worn it, so you won't understand
한 번도 입어본 적이 없으니 이해하지 못할 거예요.
You look more handsome like this
이렇게 보니 더 잘생겼네
Have you ever told your ex-boyfriend?
전 남자친구에게 말한 적 있나요?
You are heavy
당신은 무거워요
Have you ever told your ex?
전 애인에게 말한 적 있나요?
Impossible
불가능한
No one has ever lifted me up like this, never before
지금까지 누구도 나를 이렇게 들어올려준 적이 없었습니다.
But you will be the first boy to say that
하지만 그런 말을 하는 남자는 네가 처음이 될 거야
I think it has potential
잠재력이 있다고 생각해요
force..
힘..
Is it that bad? I don't use it
그렇게 나쁜가요? 나는 그것을 사용하지 않습니다
I really can't bear the pain.. it hurts so much
정말 고통을 참을 수 없어.. 너무 아프다
Hello sister
안녕하세요 언니
So he acted to make him uncomfortable
그래서 그 사람이 자기를 불편하게 하는 행동을 했어.
Well, not like that
글쎄, 그렇지는 않아
I know it doesn't hurt that much
별로 아프지 않다는 걸 알아
When you get home, put ice for 48 hours
집에 오면 48시간 동안 얼음을 넣어두세요
If it still hurts
그래도 아프다면
Apply a little medicine to improve blood circulation
혈액순환을 좋게 하는 약을 조금 바르세요
Don't walk, you know?
걷지 마세요, 아시죠?
Thank you doctor
감사합니다 의사님
Your girlfriend
당신의 여자 친구
Although quite handsome
꽤 잘생겼지만
I can't seem to love.. my heart is hard
사랑을 못하나봐요.. 마음이 힘들어요
Don't say that, doctor
그런 말 하지 마세요, 박사님
He is not stubborn
그는 고집이 세지 않다
The girl is very protective of him
그 소녀는 그를 매우 보호합니다.
He has no heart
그 사람은 심장이 없어
Why is it taking so long?
왜 이렇게 오래 걸리나요?
He must have paid for the medicine
그 사람이 약값을 지불한 게 틀림없어
He didn't leave me
그 사람은 나를 떠나지 않았어
I still can't walk
난 아직도 걸을 수 없어
Powerful medicine
강력한 약
Doctor
의사
Can you get into the car by yourself now?
이제 혼자 차에 탈 수 있나요?
(Kunkyi)
(쿤키)
(Xian.. are you still in touch with Pailing)
(시안.. 아직도 페일링이랑 연락하시나요?)
(Your ex-girlfriend, that actress is very beautiful)
(너의 전 여자친구, 그 여배우 는 정말 아름다워)
(like this)
(이와 같이)
(Because a friend wanted him to act in a movie)
(친구가 영화에 출연하길 원했기 때문에)
(Introduce them if you don't mind )
(괜찮다면 소개해주세요 )
(Did you hear me say hello?)
(내가 인사하는 걸 들었어?)
Is he?
그는?
I think his acting is normal
내 생각엔 그의 연기는 평범해
Now the actress in my car is better
이제 내 차에 탄 여배우가 더 좋아졌어
(indeed)
(물론)
(are you in the car)
(너 차 안에 있어?)
(I won't bother you anymore, that's all)
(더 이상 귀찮게 하지 않겠습니다. 그게 전부입니다)
So his ex-girlfriend is that famous actress
그럼 그 전여친이 그 유명한 배우인거군요
His ex-boyfriend..
그의 전 남자친구..
In the car, he called me a better actress
차 안에서 그는 나에게 더 나은 배우라고 말했다
He thought I was better than him
그 사람은 내가 자기보다 낫다고 생각했지
Can you guess the meaning?
의미를 추측할 수 있나요?
He's an ex anyway
어차피 그 사람은 전남친이잖아
I have come this far
나는 여기까지 왔다
Anyway, I can't give up now
어쨌든 이제 포기할 수 없어
My daughter is doing it on purpose
딸아이가 일부러 그러는 거에요
My daughter-in-law doesn't like hot pop
며느리는 핫팝을 별로 안 좋아해요
How do you know?
어떻게 알 수 있나요?
Xian
시안
My uncle and daughter are about to finish eating, have you come now?
삼촌과 딸이 식사를 마치려는데 이제 오셨나요?
Because there are things to do
할 일이 있으니까
Don't forget the others and he arrived very late
다른 사람들도 잊지 마세요. 그는 매우 늦게 도착했어요
Avoid
피하다
I haven't seen my daughter for a long time
오랫동안 내 딸을 보지 못했어요
I don't want to see my daughter getting fat now
이제 내 딸이 살찌는 걸 보고 싶지 않아요
Tell me the story of the daughter . What happened between the daughter and the senior?
딸의 이야기를 들려주세요. 딸과 선배 사이에 무슨 일이 있었던 걸까요?
Oh, I know about this matter
아, 나도 이 문제에 대해 알아요
I misunderstood him
나는 그를 오해했다
I sent a friend to Wiche to apologize to him
나는 Wiche에게 사과하기 위해 친구를 보냈습니다.
Unexpectedly, as soon as he accepted, my daughter
뜻밖에도 그가 수락하자마자 내 딸은
He was even invited to a concert
콘서트에 초대되기도 했고
I was very surprised
나는 매우 놀랐다
Did he invite you to the concert today?
그가 오늘 콘서트에 당신을 초대했나요?
Yes
예
But it's a bit strange
그런데 좀 이상하네요
It was as if he had not invited his daughter
마치 딸을 초대하지 않은 것 같았어요
But there was no problem, the daughters were happy
하지만 문제는 없었어요. 딸들은 행복했어요
You misunderstood him
당신은 그를 오해했습니다
And I went to the concert with him without even feeling guilty
그리고 나는 그 사람과 함께 콘서트에 죄책감도 느끼지 않고 갔다
Why are you holding back?
왜 주저하고 있습니까?
Always with grudges
언제나 원한을 품고
For my sister's successful performance
언니의 성공적인 공연을 위해
- Let's drink
- 마시자
(don't forget)
(잊지 마세요)
(I haven't paid you hospital fees yet)
(아직 병원비 안 냈어요)
Young mother is dating the actress again
젊은 엄마가 여배우와 다시 데이트하고 있습니다
Don't say no
아니라고 말하지 마세요
Ku Kyi said that there is a princess in U Xung's car
Ku Kyi는 U Xung의 차에 공주가 있다고 말했습니다.
I just saw that he sent a message to U Young
방금 유영한테 문자 보낸 걸 봤는데
Who is Shi Xian?
시시안은 누구인가?
Is it someone I know?
내가 아는 사람인가요?
Don't pay attention to what my sister is saying
내 여동생이 하는 말에 귀 기울이지 마세요.
Just saw it for sure
방금 봤는데 확실히 나오네
Got it... Don't believe the rumors so easily
알았어... 소문을 너무 쉽게 믿지마
Gossip spreads like that
소문은 그렇게 퍼진다
She knew what she was doing
그녀는 자신이 무엇을 하고 있는지 알고 있었습니다.
But in love
하지만 사랑에
You can preserve them by cherishing them
소중히 여기면 보존할 수 있다
Xian
시안
If you meet the right girl
좋은 여자 만나면
Love him and don't lose him
그를 사랑하고 그를 잃지 마세요
Oh, Uncle Chen will have a family dinner tomorrow night, won't he?
아, 첸 삼촌이 내일 밤에 가족 저녁 식사를 하실 거예요, 그렇죠?
If you don't have a pair, take Xiaoyu with you
짝이 없다면 샤오위를 데리고 가세요
No need
필요 없음
I want to go with my younger daughter
작은 딸과 함께 가고 싶어요
Not everyone can get along with my uncle
모두가 내 삼촌과 잘 지낼 수는 없어
Now whispering
지금 속삭이는 중
Eat, sister
먹어요 언니
I'm going to the restroom
나는 화장실에 갈거야
Cold
추운
Something is happening to him
그에게 무슨 일이 일어나고 있어요
It's okay, just eat..
괜찮아 그냥 먹어..
(I think he has a girlfriend)
(내 생각엔 그 사람 여자친구가 있는 것 같아)
(Which actress I have to investigate)
(내가 조사해야 할 여배우는 누구인가)
(Are you Shi Xian?)
(당신은 Shi Xian입니까?)
(who could it be)
(누가 그럴까요)
(How much does medicine cost?)
(약값은 얼마입니까?)
(I'll hand it over)
(내가 넘겨줄게)
What kind of hospital is it? It's so expensive
어떤 병원인가요? 너무 비싸요
(Can I use health insurance?)
(건강보험을 이용할 수 있나요?)
(good manners)
(좋은 매너)
(Regard it as today's wages)
(오늘의 급여로 간주)
I'm an Oscar-level actor
나는 오스카급 배우
Just over two thousand?
2천 조금 넘게요?
A less sticky person
덜 끈끈한 사람
(My Oscar level acting)
(내 오스카급 연기)
(Just over two thousand?)
(2천 조금 넘게?)
(how much do you want)
(얼마를 원하세요?)
(I want you to have dinner with me tomorrow)
(내일 같이 저녁 먹자고 해요)
I often say it
자주 하는 말인데
(Yes, I will pick you up tomorrow at 5 pm)
(네, 내일 오후 5시에 데리러 갈게요)
(what will we eat)
(우리는 무엇을 먹을 것인가)
(Which pair to wear)
(어떤 켤레를 입을까)
(Which one goes with me)
(나랑 같이 갈 사람은 누구야?)
(red)
(빨간색)
Is it red?
빨간색인가요?
Where does the red come from?
빨간색은 어디서 나오는 걸까요?
Is he kidding me?
농담하는 걸까요?
Or is it Kala Blaine?
아니면 칼라 블레인인가요?
Didn't he say that little red boy?
그 작은 빨간 소년이 말하지 않았나요?
Clear.. Is this shirt beautiful?
그렇군요.. 이 셔츠 예쁘나요?
It's quite beautiful
꽤 아름답습니다
(What is he doing here?)
(그 사람 여기서 뭐 하는 거야?)
- Hello - (Sister Shuyi)
- 안녕하세요 - (슈이 자매)
(What are you doing? Want to go shopping with me?)
(뭐하세요? 나랑 쇼핑하러 갈래요?)
I'm already shopping
나 벌써 쇼핑 중이야
I even met that liar and his girlfriend
그 거짓말쟁이와 그 여자친구도 만났어
What a misfortune
정말 불행한 일이군요
(Really, where is my sister now?)
(정말, 내 여동생은 지금 어디 있지?)
In Kojin
In Kojin
I am the worst
나는 최악이다
Every time I see them
나는 그들을 볼 때마다
I want to wash my eyes for days
며칠간 눈을 씻고 싶다
(Kojin...)
(Kojin...)
(Wait, I'm here)
(잠깐만요, 나 여기 있어요)
This shirt is so plain, isn't it?
이 셔츠 너무 평범하지 않나요?
That's for the middle-aged.. not for me
그건 중년을 위한 거고.. 나한테는 아니야
The choice is not good
선택이 좋지 않네요
With a plunging neckline, my makeup goes on easily
깊게 파인 네크라인으로 메이크업이 잘 지워지네요
Choose another fabric
다른 원단을 선택하세요
"I'll run out of makeup."
"화장 다 지워지겠다."
Is this shirt too casual?
이 셔츠는 너무 캐주얼한가요?
There is no design style
디자인 스타일이 없습니다.
No.. The simple stitch is elegant and attractive
아니요.. 심플한 스티치가 우아하고 매력적이에요
Look at my sister's bright red skin
내 여동생의 새빨간 피부를 보세요
Chinese New Year is coming
구정이 다가오고 있습니다
Visiting relatives, this color is the best
친척집 가는데 이 색이 제일 좋음
But the shoulder area feels the same
근데 어깨 부분은 똑같은 느낌이에요
clear
분명한
Does this look good with me?
이게 나한테 좋아 보이는데?
Looks good
좋아 보인다
I'll put on another one
하나 더 입을게요
My sister.. This dress is exactly like my sister
내 여동생.. 이 드레스가 내 여동생이랑 똑같아
My sister is very white
내 여동생은 매우 하얗다
This bright red looks like it's perfect for skin tones like my sister's
밝은 레드 색상이 저희 언니 같은 피부톤에 잘 어울리는 것 같아요
It looks even better than the magazine models
잡지 모델보다 더 잘생겼네요
thank you
감사합니다
I want to take a picture to show my friend
친구에게 보여주려고 사진을 찍고 싶어요
Solid phase batteries
고체상 배터리
Limiting and delaying the development of the new energy vehicle industry
신에너지 자동차 산업의 발전을 제한하고 지연시키는 것
In business
사업
We're going to see half-solid batteries appear
우리는 반고체 배터리가 나타나는 것을 보게 될 것입니다
China will produce large quantities of semi-solid batteries
중국, 반고체 배터리 대량 생산한다
Probably the first company
아마도 최초의 회사일 것이다.
This time the financing is very important for them
이번에는 자금조달이 그들에게 매우 중요합니다
Kellan's semi-solid batteries have strong technology
켈란의 ​​반고체전지는 강력한 기술력을 갖고 있습니다.
Current generation of high power batteries
현재 세대의 고전력 배터리
They can be considered leaders
그들은 리더로 간주 될 수 있습니다
Okay, you all have done your homework
알았어, 다들 숙제를 다 했어
I react according to the situation
나는 상황에 따라 반응한다.
We must participate in national carbon dioxide targets
우리는 국가 이산화탄소 목표에 참여해야 합니다
(does it look good)
(좋아 보이는가?)
(Answer only one letter)
(한 글자만 답해주세요)
Are you smiling?
당신은 웃고 있나요?
Why are you smiling?
왜 웃고 있어요?
It's nothing
아무것도 아니야
So, do you have an appointment this evening?
그럼 오늘 저녁에 약속이 있나요?
I can go with you.. I don't have an appointment
같이 갈 수 있어요.. 약속이 없어요
I'm not going with you
난 너랑 안 갈 거야
It's interesting
흥미 롭군